good morning I'm gonna owe him or him
four shots and the CEO of Prudential
Insurance Malaysia Berhad a prudential
malaysia'
we believe that positive energy coming
from the Morning Sun is always shining
at us hence regardless the hour of the
day it is always morning this is the
culture we believe at conventions as an
insurer our mission is to provide
financial freedom and peace of mind for
all Malaysians Prudential is a huge
organization with tons of opportunity to
learn develop and obscure myself in both
my career and personal development for
me Prudential has given me a lot of
opportunities to grow and improve myself
there are a lot of experienced
colleagues you can learn from and the
best of it all is that they're all
willing to help each other up with a
smile
working in Prudential pricing has taught
me a lot of things including the
technical knowledge as well as soft
skill potential pricing has a fast-paced
work environment working one year in
Prudential pricing has exposed me to the
actual pricing book I had a hands-on
experience in developing as well as
launching the new financial solutions
throughout the process I have been
working with colleagues 400 departments
which improved my communication skills
to convert those accurate advert on to
element
potential has a strong rich heritage but
we are also an ambitious forward-looking
company our vision needs to be the
number one insurer in the hearts and
minds of our people and customers people
are our greatest assets because without
great people we cannot deliver great
products and services what company are
you looking to join this is a company
that provides support dreams don't your
talents and has a responsibility for all
if you are looking for a job that
excites allows you to grow and rewards
you look no further than Prudential
secondly would be the people even though
they are challenging times the people
here helps you get through it all
I'm indeed very thankful for the
opportunities and friendship that I've
gained in my journey with potential this
kind of environment is what really
motivates me to work hard and improve
myself because I know I have a lot of
support behind me I feel that no matter
where you work you'll always be facing
difficulties and stressful times so it's
always great to have a friendly and
positive environment another important
element that helps me for my career
growth is the supportive colleagues in
organization people working around me
always offer me help whenever I'm in
dock this friendly working women really
helps me to reduce the work tension
see you in London at the Malaysian
career fair 2019